> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 所以我再给你看一个有误差的地方
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I'm gonna show you one
more thing here with error boundaries,
这样我就能给你展示组件更新
just so I can show you componentDidUpdate.
你知道的你完全可以这样做
Now, just so you know, you could
totally instead of do this with just
componentDidCatch 不使用 componentDidUpdate。
componentDidCatch and
not use componentDidUpdate.
但我想展示如何使用 componentDidUpdate。
But I just wanna show you how
to use componentDidUpdate.
所以在 componentDidCatch 下面，输入 componentDidUpdate，
So under componentDidCatch here,
put componentDidUpdate,
所以你可以看到这里有几种生命周期的方法
so you can see here there's actually
quite a few lifecycle methods.
如果您有兴趣了解有关生命周期方法的更多信息，
If you're interested in learning
more about lifecycle methods,
你可以查看这个课程的较旧版本，对吧 ?
you can actually check out older
versions of this course, right?
所以我深入的，但通常是 componentDidMount 是你可以用的
So I go over them in depth but normally
componentDidMount is one that you can use
要把事情安排好，跟其他图书馆整合一下。
quite a bit to set things up,
integrate with other libraries.
这是你第一次开始的时候
It's what you run when you first start.
componentDidUpdate，您仍在使用，但不一定如此。
componentDidUpdate, you still use but
not necessarily as much.
这将会对一些更新做出反应，我将在这里展示第二个信息。
This will be reacting to kind of updates,
which I'll show you here in just a second.
componentWillUnmount，如果您执行 setInterval 或
componentWillUnmount, if
you do a setInterval or
如果你要清理任何东西
if you have to clean up anything,
这将允许您在组件离开 DOM 之前清除内容。
this will allow you to clean up things
before the component leaves the DOM.
然后还有几个这些
And then there's a couple
of these as well,
>> Brian Holt: 与组件相似
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Like component will
接收道具，就像我要接收全新的道具。
receive props, it's like I'm
about to receive brand new props.
然后还有其他的那些不安全的
And then there's some other ones
in here as well, the unsafe ones,
那些不允许你使用的东西好吗
which react.stricts will
not allow you to use, okay?
还记得我们在整个申请中都放了反反剂
And remember we put react.stricts
around our entire application,
它会警告你，所以 >> Brian Holt: 好的，所以
it'll warn you about that, so
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
我们现在要做的就是要做 componentWillUpdate
what we're gonna do now is we're
gonna do componentWillUpdate.
> > Brian Holt: 接下来我们要做的就是每一个
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And what we're gonna do
here is this is gonna get run every single
获取新状态或新道具的时间。
time that it gets new state or new props.
所以在这件案子里我想说如果是 state.hasError ，那么
So in this case,
I'm gonna say if this.state.hasError, so
如果有什么东西更新了这件事就会出错
if something updates this and
now this has an error,
我想让你做 setTimeOut
what I want you to do is I
want you to do setTimeOut.
然后给它一个箭头函数
And give it an arrow function and
say this.setState 重定向， >> Brian Holt: true，
say this.setState redirect,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: true,
然后等待 5000 毫秒。
and then wait for 5000 milliseconds.
>> Brian Holt: 因此， >> Brian Holt: 此处的 setTimeout ，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: The setTimeout here,
它将运行此功能 5000 秒或 5，000 秒后
it's going to run this function and
after 5,000 seconds or 5,000
以毫秒计它会设置状态以便重定向将为 true。
milliseconds rather it's gonna setStates
so that redirect is gonna be true.
所以我们先到这里吧
So let's go ahead up here
in the state up here,
将重定向， >> Brian Holt: False 放在第 7 行。
put redirect,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: False on line 7 there.
>> Brian Holt: 然后我们想做什么
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then what we wanna do
在这里， >> Brian Holt: 我们想做的第一件事是
here,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Is the first thing we wanna
问，这里的秩序很重要。
ask, and
the order here is quite important.
你得说如果 this.state.redirect ，
You're gonna have to say,
if this.state.redirect,
我们要做的就是要回去
then what we're gonna do
is we're going to return,
>> Brian Holt: 重定向组件，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: A redirect component which
来自 reachRouter 和
comes from reachRouter and
我们会把重定向到/
we're gonna say redirect to/
>> Brian Holt: 如你想象的那样
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: As you might imagine,
每当您呈现重定向时
whenever you render a redirect,
只是把路由器重定向到别的地方吧
it just redirects the router
to be somewhere else, right?
您也可以以编程方式执行此操作。
You can also do this programmatically.
我完全可以说，你不用复制这个，我觉得它是在航行中。
I could have totally said, and you don't
have to copy this, I think it's navigate.
>> Brian Holt: 就像这样，这也会起作用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Like that, and
this would have worked as well.
导航也来自达能路由器
And navigate comes from
reachRouter as well, but
我想向你们展示这两种方法。
I wanted to show you
both ways of doing that.
>> Brian Holt: 您不需要 componentWillUpdate，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You don't
want componentWillUpdate,
您需要 componentDidUpdate。
you want componentDidUpdate.
>> Brian Holt: 这两个操作都将工作，但我们要执行 componentDidUpdate。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Both of these will work but
let's do componentDidUpdate.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，然后再做一个人为错误。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and then let's
go make an artificial error again.
就在这里而不是 componenttDidMount
So just here instead
of componenttDidMount,
我们会说新错误
we'll say throw new Error.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，现在 5 秒后，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
now after 5 seconds,
它应该重定向回主页，它会这样做。
it should redirect back to the home page,
which it does.